<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title/><link>https://example.com/</link><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description/><generator>HugoBlox Kit (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://example.com/media/logo.svg</url><title/><link>https://example.com/</link></image><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://example.com/about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/about/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="the-short-version"&gt;The Short Version&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am a &lt;strong&gt;Director of Software Engineering&lt;/strong&gt; with 17 years of experience, currently leading a remote-first department of &lt;strong&gt;150+ engineers&lt;/strong&gt; across 18 squads.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I specialize in &lt;strong&gt;scale&lt;/strong&gt;. whether that&amp;rsquo;s scaling software architectures to handle thousands of enterprise tenants, scaling teams from local units to global powerhouses, or scaling release frequencies by &lt;strong&gt;1500%&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id="my-journey"&gt;My Journey&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My career didn&amp;rsquo;t start in a computer lab; it started in my parents&amp;rsquo; living room at age 8. I reprogrammed the family satellite receiver to unlock more channels. My Dad was furious until he saw the selection - then he just asked for the remote.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That curiosity never left. It evolved from hacking hardware to building enterprise software, architecting Chip &amp;amp; Pin solutions, and now, defining technical strategy for global SaaS platforms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently, at &lt;strong&gt;SS&amp;amp;C Blue Prism&lt;/strong&gt;, I own the engineering delivery across the entire product portfolio. This involves a delicate balancing act: maintaining the &amp;ldquo;Current Gen&amp;rdquo; revenue drivers while architecting the &amp;ldquo;Next-Gen&amp;rdquo; cloud-native future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="impact-by-the-numbers"&gt;Impact by the Numbers&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I believe engineering leadership is measured by outcomes, not just output. Some highlights from my recent work include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;150+&lt;/strong&gt; - Engineers, Managers, and Leads in my current department.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;500%&lt;/strong&gt; - Increase in release cycle speed achieved through modern CI/CD.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;15x&lt;/strong&gt; - Increase in deployment frequency by shifting to a &amp;ldquo;DevOps First&amp;rdquo; mindset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;300%&lt;/strong&gt; - Expansion of the engineering department engineered via global recruitment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id="how-i-lead"&gt;How I Lead&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While I focus on strategy today, I remain deeply technical. I believe you cannot direct what you do not understand. Then again, Technology is easy; it&amp;rsquo;s people that are hard. My leadership philosophy is built on three pillars:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Psychological Safety&lt;/strong&gt;: Innovation requires failure. I build cultures where teams feel safe to experiment, providing they learn from the result.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Autonomy with Alignment&lt;/strong&gt;: I set the destination (Strategy) and the guardrails (Standards), then trust my leaders to find the best route.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Commercial Awareness&lt;/strong&gt;: Engineering is expensive. I champion &lt;strong&gt;FinOps&lt;/strong&gt; strategies to ensure every line of code we ship drives measurable business value.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id="beyond-the-terminal"&gt;Beyond the Terminal&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I&amp;rsquo;m not optimizing pipelines or mentoring leaders, I am usually:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🐈 Wrangling one of my 4 cats (Yes, 4!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🎮 Gaming on Steam (Ask me about my current obsession).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🥐 Baking (Engineering you can eat).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🤖 Smart Home tech (I spend an unhealthy amount of time trying to get my vacuum cleaner to negotiate a peace treaty with my cat-flap.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🖨️ 3D Printing (Turning perfectly good spools of filament into &amp;lsquo;abstract art&amp;rsquo;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3 id="lets-connect"&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s Connect&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am always open to discussing engineering leadership, the future of AI in education, or the nuances of legacy migration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
|
&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>bcrypt.net Core</title><link>https://example.com/projects/bcrypt-dotnet-core/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/projects/bcrypt-dotnet-core/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;At the release of .NET Core 1.0, there was no way to trivially use bcrypt password hashing. A .NET library existed, but it had been abandoned by the author.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I took it upon myself to port this library to .NET Core. I have been maintaining it ever since and it is currently the most popular bcrypt library for .NET Core!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="key-features"&gt;Key Features&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full bcrypt password hashing support for .NET Core&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compatible with the original BCrypt.Net library&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cross-platform support (Windows, Linux, macOS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Regular updates and maintenance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comprehensive test coverage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id="impact"&gt;Impact&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This library has become the go-to solution for bcrypt password hashing in the .NET Core ecosystem, with millions of downloads and widespread adoption across enterprise and open-source projects.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>